* |
* |
* |
* |

* |
* |
* [USD](javascript:void(0))
* |
* [Login](javascript:void(0))

[

Softronics Easy. Flexible. Close](https://www.softronics.ch/en)

Online Storage
--------------

Your fast and versatile cloud storage for all tasks. Access from any device – simply and intuitively. Supports integration via WebDAV.

Choose from multiple locations.

[#### MyDrive

Server located in Switzerland.](https://www.softronics.ch/en/products/online-storage?l=ch)[#### MyDrive

Price advantage location Europe.](https://www.softronics.ch/en/products/online-storage?l=eu)

FTP Storage
-----------

This cloud storage is aimed at technically proficient users and enables fast data exchange via the FTP protocol. With transfer speeds of up to 500 Mbit/s, it is particularly efficient. The storage is also available under your own domain.

Choose from multiple locations.

[#### Swiss Premium FTP

Server located in Switzerland.](https://www.softronics.ch/en/products/ftp-storage?l=ch)[#### Premium FTP

Price advantage location Europe.](https://www.softronics.ch/en/products/ftp-storage?l=eu)

Virtual Server
--------------

Our latest-generation virtual servers offer maximum performance, fast NVMe storage, maximum security and flexible use. Install and use your applications as required.

Choose from multiple locations.

[#### Swiss Premium Server

Server located in Switzerland.](https://www.softronics.ch/en/products/virtual-server?l=ch)[#### Premium Server

Price advantage location Europe.](https://www.softronics.ch/en/products/virtual-server?l=eu)

[Domains
-------

Register your desired domain quickly and easily. Choose from over 700 domain extensions at attractive conditions.](https://www.softronics.ch/en/products/domains)

    [Online Storage
    --------------](https://www.softronics.ch/en/products/online-storage)
    
    Your fast and versatile cloud storage for all tasks. Access from any device – simply and intuitively. Supports integration via WebDAV.
    
    Choose from multiple locations.
    
    [#### MyDrive
    
    Server located in Switzerland.](https://www.softronics.ch/en/products/online-storage?l=ch)[#### MyDrive
    
    Price advantage location Europe.](https://www.softronics.ch/en/products/online-storage?l=eu)

    [FTP Storage
    -----------](https://www.softronics.ch/en/products/ftp-storage)
    
    This cloud storage is aimed at technically proficient users and enables fast data exchange via the FTP protocol. With transfer speeds of up to 500 Mbit/s, it is particularly efficient. The storage is also available under your own domain.
    
    Choose from multiple locations.
    
    [#### Swiss Premium FTP
    
    Server located in Switzerland.](https://www.softronics.ch/en/products/ftp-storage?l=ch)[#### Premium FTP
    
    Price advantage location Europe.](https://www.softronics.ch/en/products/ftp-storage?l=eu)

    [Virtual Server
    --------------](https://www.softronics.ch/en/products/virtual-server)
    
    Our latest-generation virtual servers offer maximum performance, fast NVMe storage, maximum security and flexible use. Install and use your applications as required.
    
    Choose from multiple locations.
    
    [#### Swiss Premium Server
    
    Server located in Switzerland.](https://www.softronics.ch/en/products/virtual-server?l=ch)[#### Premium Server
    
    Price advantage location Europe.](https://www.softronics.ch/en/products/virtual-server?l=eu)

    [Domains
    -------](https://www.softronics.ch/en/products/domains)
    
    Register your desired domain quickly and easily. Choose from over 700 domain extensions at attractive conditions.

State-of-the-art **Cloud solutions**  
by Softronics
====================================================

Privacy Policy
==============

Welcome to Softronics Communication AG
--------------------------------------

We are pleased that you are visiting our website and thank you for your interest in our world-class products, services, websites and mobile applications (collectively, our "Services"). Data protection and data security when using our website are very important to us. We therefore inform you here about which of your personal data we collect when you visit our website and for what purposes it is used.

Since changes in the law or changes in our internal company processes may make it necessary to adapt our privacy policy, we ask you to read through our privacy policy on a regular basis. The privacy policy can be accessed, saved and printed out at any time under Privacy Policy.

1\. General
-----------

This privacy policy applies to all services provided by Softronics Communication AG, based on the Swiss New Federal Act on Data Protection of September 1, 2023.  
  
The responsible entity is:  
  
Softronics Communication AG  
St. Dionysstrasse 31  
8645 Rapperswil-Jona  
Switzerland  
  
Please direct any inquiries regarding data protection to [Softronics](https://www.softronics.ch/en/support/contact-form).

2\. Processing of your personal data
------------------------------------

We generally process personal data in accordance with Swiss data protection laws in Switzerland. We use and store your personal data only for processing your inquiries, orders and for contacting you.

### Data collected by us

* IP address and region of the connecting computer
* Date and time of access
* Name and URL of the accessed data
* Website from which the access is made (referrer URL)
* Browser used and, if applicable, the operating system of your computer, as well as the name of your access provider

Furthermore, your contact details are stored when you register with us.

* Company
* Title
* Street
* Email address
* First name & Surname
* ZIP and City
* Your reference
* Your Comments

The legal basis for this processing is Art. 6 para. 1 lit. f GDPR.

3\. Registration data for orders
--------------------------------

As part of your order with us, we need to collect and process certain personal data from you as your registration data. When paying by credit card or other online payments, we do not collect or store payment transaction information such as credit card numbers or verification numbers. You only provide this information directly to the respective payment service provider. We delete your data as soon as you delete your user account with us or when the legal retention periods have expired.  
You can delete your user account yourself in the Settings or by sending us an email to [Softronics](https://www.softronics.ch/en/support/contact-form), with a request for deletion. The legal basis for this processing is Art. 6 para. 1 lit. b GDPR.

4\. Website -Tracking and Cookies
---------------------------------

This website partly uses so-called cookies. These serve to make the service more user-friendly, effective and secure. Cookies are small text files that the browser places and stores on your computer. You can prevent the storage of so-called cookies by making the appropriate setting in your browser software. However, we would like to point out that in this case not all functions of this website can be used to their full extent.

5\. Disclosure of personal data
-------------------------------

In addition to the controller, external service providers who assist us in providing our services may have access to your data. Occasionally, other third parties such as authorities, external consultants or certain business partners may receive your data.

**In detail, these include:**  

### Online payments

For online payments, e.g. by credit card or TWINT, the payment is processed by an external service provider. For online payment, your details will be collected directly by the service provider Worldline Switzerland Ltd, Hardturmstrasse 201, CH-8005 Zurich.

### Third countries

Data transfers to third countries take place in compliance with the legally regulated admissibility requirements. If the transfer of data to a third country is not for the performance of our contract with you, we do not have your consent, the transfer is not necessary for the assertion, exercise or defense of legal claims, and no other exemption applies, we will only transfer your data to a third country if an adequacy decision pursuant to Article 45 GDPR or appropriate safeguards pursuant to Article 46 GDPR are in place. One of these adequacy decisions is the so-called "Privacy Shield" for the USA. For transfers to companies certified under the Privacy Shield, the level of data protection is generally considered adequate within the meaning of Article 45 of the GDPR. As a rule, however, we do not rely on the Privacy Shield, but create appropriate safeguards pursuant to Art. 46 of the GDPR and an adequate level of data protection by concluding the EU standard data protection clauses issued by the European Commission with the receiving entity.

### Additional recipients

Government agencies and courts, provided that there is a legal obligation for the disclosure. According to Art. 6 para. 1 p. 1 lit. c GDPR

6\. Data protection laws
------------------------

Our partners have obligated themselves to comply with the applicable data protection regulations towards us. Order processing contracts have been concluded in accordance with Art 28 GDPR.  
The protection of your data is of great concern to us. Therefore, we use technical and organizational security measures to protect the stored personal data against accidental or intentional manipulation, loss or destruction and against access by unauthorized parties. Our security measures are continuously reviewed and improved in line with technical progress.

7\. Social media data
---------------------

### YouTube

We integrate the videos of the platform "YouTube" of the provider Google LLC, 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, USA. Privacy policy: https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/, Opt-Out: https://adssettings.google.com/authenticated.

8\. Website analytics
---------------------

We use Matomo Open Analytics Platform, on the basis of our legitimate interests (i.e. interest in the analysis, optimization and economic operation of our online offer within the meaning of Art. 6 para. 1 lit. f. GDPR). GDPR) Matomo Open Analytics Platform, https://matomo.org/. Matomo uses so-called cookies. The information generated by the cookie about the use of the online offer by the users is transmitted exclusively to our servers and stored. Users can prevent the storage of cookies by setting their browser software accordingly. The personal data of the users are stored anonymously.

9\. Data subject rights
-----------------------

You have the right to request information about the personal data we process about you. When requesting information, we ask for your understanding that we may then require proof from you that you are the person you claim to be. Furthermore, you have a right to rectification or deletion or to restriction of processing, insofar as you are entitled to this by law. Furthermore, you have a right to object to processing within the scope of the law. The same applies to a right to data portability.

10\. Right of appeal
--------------------

You have the right to complain about the processing of personal data by us to a data protection supervisory authority.

11\. Data security and backup measures
--------------------------------------

We are committed to protecting your privacy and keeping your personal information confidential. To prevent manipulation, loss or misuse of your data stored with us, we take extensive technical and organizational security precautions, which are regularly reviewed and adapted to technological progress. This includes, among other things, the use of recognized encryption methods (SSL or TLS, particularly with Hypertext Transfer Protocol Secure, abbreviated to https). However, we would like to point out that, due to the structure of the Internet, it is possible that the rules of data protection and the above-mentioned security measures are not observed by other persons or institutions not within our sphere of responsibility. In particular, data disclosed unencrypted - e.g., if this is done by e-mail - can be read by third parties. We have no technical influence on this. It is the user's responsibility to protect the data he or she provides against misuse by encrypting it or in any other way.

12\. Voluntary provision of data
--------------------------------

There is no legal obligation for the provision of your data to Softronics Communication AG. However, you will not be able to use certain services from us if you do not provide us with your data. The provision of your data is completely voluntary.

_Published on 28/03/2024_

### Softronics

### Products

### Other

### Contact

Softronics Communication AG  
St. Dionysstrasse 31  
CH-8645 Rapperswil-Jona  

* * *

© 1997 - 2024  Softronics Communication AG
